Guide to the Frank Durkan Papers AIA.008
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series IV: Legal Cases, 1975-2003
  - Subseries J: Shah of Iran
    - Legal: Statement of Defense of the United States: Islamic Republic of Iran v. The United States, Jun 10, 1983 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Legal: Statement of Defense: Exhibits, 1979-1981, 1983 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Subseries K. U.S. v. McKinley et al (McKinley, McColgan, McCann, and Moley)
    In 1990, Kevin Joseph McKinley, Seamus McColgan, Sean John McCann, and Seamus Moley were arrested in Florida and charged with buying an anti-aircraft missile and other weapons from undercover agents with the intention of providing the weapons to members of the Provisional IRA in Northern Ireland. They were found guilty and in 1991, McKinley, McColgan, and Moley were sentenced to 51 months in prison. Frank Durkan represented the defendants, along with attorney Michael Dowd.
    - Additional Government Discovery, Nov 20, 1990 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Amnesty International Reports, Jun 1991 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Alcohol, Tobacco, and Firearms (ATF) Investigations, circa 1989-1991 (Box 35, Folder 10, Folder 11)
    - Baldy, Tom F. Battle for Ulster, 1987 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Boyle, Francis A.: Correspondence [RESTRICTED], 1990 (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - Boyle, Francis A. "The Decolonization of Northern Ireland", 1991 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Character Letters, 1990-1991 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Clippings, 1987-1991 (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, 1990-1994 (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence and Memoranda [RESTRICTED], 1990 (Box 37, Folder 18, Folder 19)
    - Customs Service Investigation Reports, 1989 (Box 35, Folder 17, Folder 19, Folder 18)
    - Exhibits, 1990 (Box 35, Folder 20)
    - Investigative Reports, 1985-1987 (Box 35, Folder 21, Folder 23, Folder 22, Folder 24)
    - Memorandum in Opposition, 1990 (Box 35, Folder 25)
    - Motions: Defense, 1990 (Box 35, Folder 26)
    - Motions: Government, 1990 (Box 35, Folder 27, Folder 29, Folder 28, Folder 30)
    - Norwegian Helsinki Committee Report, 1990 (Box 35, Folder 32)
    - Notice of Objections, Feb 20, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 31)
    - Proceedings, 1990 (Box 36, Folder 1, Folder 2, Box 35, Folder 33, Folder 3)
    - Proceedings, Jan 19, 1990 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Proceedings, Jun 7, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Related Cases, 1982 (Box 36, Folder 6, Folder 7, Folder 8)
    - Sentencing, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 9, Folder 10, Folder 11)
    - Wiretap Summary, 1990 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Wiretap Transcripts, 1989-1990 (Box 36, Folder 18, Folder 17, Folder 16, Folder 15, Folder 22, Folder 21, Folder 20, Folder 19, Folder 13, Folder 14)
- Series V. Durkan: Personal Files and Research, Written Work & Materials of Interest, 1920, 1957-2006
  This series contains material on topics of interest to Durkan, including the Great Famine in Ireland, shipwrecks of Irish coming to the Americas, his membership and activities in the Irish History Roundtable and a collection of his books, legal, history and sports-related. Also included is correspondence to and from Durkan on a a wide range of topics from letters to the editors of various publications and opinion pieces to letters of recommendation and personal matters. Additionally, a small collection of books which apparently belonged to Paul O'Dwyer, his uncle and head of the firm in which Durkan practiced law, are included in this series, many signed and/or annotated by the author.
  - Subseries A. Correspondence, Subject Files and Writings
    This series contains correspondence to and from Durkan, articles, speeches and letters to the editors, materials on topics of interest to Durkan and a few photographs. Materials in Box 29 were in very bad condition and most of the originals have been photocopied.
    - 1798 Rising, 1998-2000 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - 1798 Rising: Newspaper Clippings and Articles, 1997-1998 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - 1798 Rising: Photographs, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - American Committee for Ulster Justice (ACUJ), 1974-1978 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - American Irish Unity Committee: Symposium (includes photographs), Jul 22, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Article: "The Hunger Strikers" / Hunger Strikers 25th Anniversary by Frank Durkan, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - Articles and Speeches by Durkan, undated (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Articles, Correspondence, Newspaper Clippings: general (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Ashe, Thomas: Banner unveiling (1918 Hunger Striker), Apr 2005 (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - Battle of Aughrim, 1691 (pamphlet), undated (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - Brehon Law Society, 1981-1988 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Collins, Michael: Photograph, Armagh City, Sep 5, 1921 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Committee on the Administration of Justice, 1999-2003 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence: Materials from Charlie McGrath, 1995 (Box 36, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence: Personal and Professional, 1955 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence: Personal and Professional, 1956 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence: Personal and Professional (Segregated), 1956 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence: Personal and Professional, 1963-1970 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence: Personal and Professional, 1967 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence: Personal and Professional, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence: Personal and Professional, 1976 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - County Mayo, 1992-2003 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - County Mayo Association: Yearbook, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - County Mayo Football Championship Programs, 1992-2000 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - County Mayo: Lavan, Sean Thomas (1898-1973), 1996 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - County Mayo: Newspapers, 1995-1999 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Cuimhneachan 1916 - Commemoration of the 1916 Rising. Friends of Irish Freedom and Sean Ogliagh Na Heireann Heritage Association., Apr 15, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Curran, Moira: Deportation, includes family papers, John Curran. (Hugh O'Rourke of O'Dwyer Bernstien handled this case), 1897-1981 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Duffy, Jimmy: assorted articles and documents; includes DeValera statement (photocopy) and James Shea memoirs, 1923-2002 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Duffy, Jimmy: transcription, paper re: George Harrison; poems, 2004, undated (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - East Mayo Brigade IRA: Commemorative Memorial, Apr 7, 1958 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Emmett, Robert, 2001-2004 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Emmett, Robert, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Famine Pot, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Gaelic Gotham: Correspondence, Newspaper Clippings, 1995-1996 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Gaelic Gotham: Media Package, 1995-1996 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Gaelic Gotham Report: "Assessing a Controversial Exhibition at the Museum of the City of New York, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Grosse Ile, Canada I (Famine Quarantine Island), 1994-2001 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Grosse Ile, Canada II (Famine Quarantine Island), 1994-2001 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Grosse Ile, 1984-1996 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Harrison, George, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Honors and Memberships, 1992, undated (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Horizon Halfway House, 1995 (Box 36, Folder 24)
    - Irish Famine, 1845-1850, 1995-1997 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Irish Famine Cathedral Cemetery, Scranton, PA, 1964, undated (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Irish Famine: Choctaw and Irish Together (CAIT)- International Humanitarian Organization, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - Irish Famine: County Mayo Killala Memorial, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - Irish Famine: Genocide Curriculum, 1997-1999 (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - Jenkinson, Noel: Durkan Speech at Commemoration, Nov 14, 1976 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Keane, James, 1920, 1987 (Box Shared Tamiment 030, Folder 18)
    - Kelly, Nicky, 1989-1990 (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - Laverty, Chuck: Research Query (Mayo football player), 1997 (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - Martin Sheridan Memorial Committee (Olympian; NYPD), 1908-1996 (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - Martin Sheridan Memorial Committee (Olympian; NYPD): Photographs (grave), circa 1996 (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - Mayo Society of New York, 1991-2004 (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - McDonnell, John J.: Correspondence re: Irish Memorabilia collection; includes photocopy of "The Story of the 1916 Proclamation" by John O'Connor., 1997 (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - Meagher, Thomas Francis (1823-1867): Article from Eire Ierland, Bulletin of the Department of External Affairs., 1967 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Molly Maguires, 1976-1984 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - National Graves Association (Ireland), 1981, undated (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - New York Irish History Roundtable: Article and Newspaper Clippings I, 1983-1996 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - New York Irish History Roundtable: Articles and Newspaper Clippings II, 1983-1996 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - New York Irish History Roundtable: Correspondence, 1991-1995 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - New York Irish History Roundtable: Newsletter, Calendar, 1988-2001 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Newsletters: The Irish Volunteer; Massachusetts Irish Volunteers, Ohio Irish Times, 1992-2002 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Newspaper Clippings: various, 1995-1999 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - O'Dwyer, Paul: Times Herald-Record story; photograph, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Photographs: Irish Institute, John Gaughan Commemoration; Paul O'Dwyer and Hon Gwyner Evans, Wales, 1976 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Photoprint: "Support Irish Republicans in Jail for Ireland", undated (Box 23, Box 10)
    - Research, 1914-1993 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Research Papers (by Rona Fields?): Irish Immigrants; Irish Republicanism from the 1980s?, undated (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Rural Resettlement Ireland!, 1993-1994 (Box 36, Folder 25)
    - Saint Patrick's Day Parade: Michael Flannery Controversy, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Saint Patrick's Day Parade: Michael Flannery Controversy: Newspaper Clippings, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Sharpton, Al: Irish Voice response by Durkan to "The O'Bradaigh Visa and Al Sharpton", Jun 1995 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Sinn Fein, 1995-1998 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - The Wreck of the St. John, Cohasset, MA (famine ship) 1849, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Subseries B: Books, Pamphlets and Publications
    - Aghaidh Achadh Mor: The Face of Aghamore (water damaged; some pages stuck together), undate (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - American Connection: U.S. Guns, Money and Influence in Northern Ireland. Jack Holland. Penguin Books, New York. inscription: "to the Florida Four with best wishes from Geroge Harrison", 1987 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - American Connection: U.S. Guns, Money and Influence in Northern Ireland. Jack Holland. Penguin. Dublin., 1989 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - "An Act for the Attainder of the Rebels in Ireland" Parliament, Westminster, London., 1657 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Bold Robert Emmett, 1778-1803. Sean o'Bradaigh. Irish Freedom Press. Inscription: "To Monica and Frank Salud George Harrison", 2003 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Breaking the Deadlock: A Way Out of the Northern Impasse. Robert Heatley. Fulcrum Press. Dublin., 1991 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Britain's War Machine in Ireland. Maurice Burke. Oisin Publications. New York., 1987 (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - The Committee: Political Assassination in Northern Ireland. Sean McPhilemy. Roberts Rinehart Publishers, Niwot, CO. (includes many notes and annotations), circa 1998 (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - Cory Collusion Inquiry Report. Chief Superintendent Breen and Superintendent Buchanan, Oct 2003 (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - Creating a New Ireland as Reflected in the Writings of William Hughes. Hughes Enterprises, Baltimore., 1995 (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - Dilseacht: The Story of Comdt. General Tom Macguire and the Second (All-Ireland) Dail. Ruairi O'Bradaigh. Irish Freedom Press. (2 copies) One includes inscription: "To Monica and Frank from your friend George Harrison, New York, 5.20.97", 1997 (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - Eire Nua: A New Democracy. Republican Sinn Fein., 2000 (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - Human Rights in Northern Ireland: A Helsinki Watch Report. Human Rights Watch., 1991 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Hunger Strike Commemoratives: Terence MacSwiney, 1920; 1980-1981 Hunger Strike, 1995, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Inishmurray: Gale, Stone and Fire - Portrait of a Fabled Island. Joe McGowan, Aeolus, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - An Introduction to Irish Research. Irish Ancestry: A Beginner's Guide. Bill Davis. Federation of Family Historical Societies, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - The IRA 1926-1936. Brian Hanley. Four Courts Press. Inscription: "To George, Thanks and Best Wishes from Brian Hanley Nov' 2003", 2002 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - The Irish Crisis. C. Desmond Greaves. Inernational Publishers. New York., 1972 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - The Irish in America. An Address by William T. Collins, Jusitce, Supreme Court, State of New York. At the Forum of National Democractic Club., Mar 9, 1935 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Journal of Prisoners on Prisons. Vol. 7, No. 2, 1996-1997 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - The McGarrity Papers: Revelations of the Irish revolutionary movement in Ireland and American 1900-1940. Sean Cronin. Anvil Books. Tralee. Co. Kerry, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Moore's Irish Melodies. ed. M.W. Balfe. Novello and Co., Ltd. London, undated (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - "A New Beginning: Policing in Northern Irleand" The Report of the Independent Commission on Policing for Northern Ireland. (2 copies), Sep 1999 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - North Mayo Historical Journal, Vol II, No. 1. North Mayo Historical and Archaeological Society., 1987-1988 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - "Northern Ireland: A Report to the Association of the Bar of the City of New York from a Mission of the Committee on International Human Rights.", Jun 1999 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - "Notes on Guerilla Warfare: A Handbook for Volunteers of the Irish Republican Army. IRA, 1956 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - O'Brien Pocket History of The Troubles. Brian Feeney. The O'Brien Press Ltd., Dublin., 2004 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - "Omos Do Tony D'Arcy, Galway and Sean MacNeela, Mayo", 1990 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - The Patten Commission: A Submission by the People of West Belfast at Whiterock Nov., 1998. Upper Springfield Development Trust., 1999 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - The Rock from which you were Hewn: A history of the Catholic Church in Lewis County West Virginia St. Patrick's Parish, Weston by Donal O'Donovan. McClain Pringint Company, Parsons, WV., 1989 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Sheltering the Fugitive? The Extradition of Irish Political Offenders. Michael Farrell. Mercier Press, Cork and Dublin., 1985 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Sports: Programs: Connacht Senior Football Championship Leitrim vs. New York, 2003; National Football League 2000/2001 Finals (Ireland); Victory Dinner Dance Mayo Gaelic Football Club of New York, 2005; Books: The Championship Hurling and Football 1999: The Complete Record. Brian Carthy. 1999; Famous All-Irelands Book 2. Canavaun Books. 1984. (2 folders), 1984-2005 (Box 24, Folder 20-21)
    - "Why the British Kill American Presidents" The New Federalist. Leesburg, VA., Dec 1994 (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - The Wreck of the British Queen. Robert F. Mooney. Mill Hill Press, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Years of Glory: Story of Kerry's All-Ireland Successes. John Barry and Eamon Horan. Self-published., 1977 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Subseries C: Paul O'Dwyer Book Collection
    - Arming the Protestants: The Formation of the Ulster Special Constabulary and the Royal Ulster Constabulary 1920-1927. Michael Farrell. Brandon Book Publishers, Ltd., Co, Kerry, Ireland. Inscription: To Paul O'Dwyer with best wishes Michael Farrell", 1983 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - The Battle of Long Island ("The Battle of Brooklyn"). Charles G. Teveson and Irene H. Wilson. Brooklyn Bicentennial Commission. Incription: To Paul O'Dywer with all best wished Joe Palin, Chariman", 1975 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Cage Eleven. Gerry Adams with an Introduction by Paul O'Dwyer (1993). Sheridan Square Press, New York., 1990 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - A Pathway to Peace. Gerry Adams, MP. Mercier Press. Cork and Dublin. (includes letter on Sinn Fein Letterhead from Adams), 1988 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Sandhogs: A History of the Tunnel Workers of New York. Paul E. Delaney. The Longfield Press. New York. Inscription: "To Paul O'Dwyer A fine Sandhog. One of the best friends the Sandhogs ever had. Sincerely Yours Richie Fitzsimmons" (includes Fitzsimmons' business card), 1983 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Twenty Years On. Edited by Michael Farrell. Brandon Book Publishers Ltd., Co. Kerry, Ireland. Inscription: "To Paul O'Dwyer with every best wish a colleague in the struggle for justice Michael Farrell", 1988 (Box 25, Folder 6)
- Series VI. Oversize Items
  This series contains mostly newspapers with articles relating to legal cases represented in the collection or personal interest pieces of Durkan.
  - Irish Times, Dublin, Sep 1, 1994 - Sep 2, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Irish Times articles: "Northern Ireland Settlement"; "Belfast Agreement Referendums", Apr 11, 1998, May 25, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - The Mayo News: "Mayo in the 20th Century", Dec 1999 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - New York Newsday: " "Noraid's Troubles: Michael Flannery, the founder of America's Irish Northern Aid Committee has withdrawn from the organization in a dispute over how best to support the fight for a united Ireland.", Nov 7, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - New York Times Magazine: "The Troubles That Won't Go Away" by John Lloyd., Dec 12, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Saoirse "Irish Freedom" isues: Jun, Sep 1994, Feb 1995, Aug 1999, 1994-1999 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Sunday Tribune: "Towards the New Ireland"; Sunday Times: "Ireland's Future: Resurrection?, Apr 12, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Series VII. Audio Visual Materials
  This series contains both commercial and private tapings. Cassettes must be reformated for access. Of note are two cassettes related of to Ruari O'Bradiagh: one an interview in 1977; the other pertaining to his visa denial in 1995.
  The VHS contain among others, interviews with Gerry Adams in Florida, a compilation of documentarys including one of the Guildford Fourt and the Birmingham Six and a film of a reunion of Spanish Civil War veterans in Barcelon, from George Harrison.
  - Subseries A: Cassettes
    - Brady, Sean: Free the Six. Brady Records, London. Side 1: Free the Six, Belfast Town, Grace, Leaving of Liverpool, Tommy Atkins; Side 2: My Green Valleys, Take it Down from the Mast, Tom Williams, Boston I Need You, British Justice, 1987; cuid33377 (Box 28A, Cassette 1)
    - The History of the Irish Republican Movement F.O.I.F., undated; cuid33378 (Box 28A, Cassette 2)
    - O'Bradiagh, Ruairi (approximately 14 minutes), Sep 2, 1997; cuid33379 (Box 28A, Cassette 3)
  - Subseries B: VHS
    - Ballyseedy (Co. Kerry), undated; cuid33380 (Box 27, Object 1)
    - The Committee - Dispatches, Channel 4. Includes note "Frank, This is the tape I spoke to you about. I would like to hear your commments. Owen", undated; cuid33381 (Box 27, Object 2)
    - Committee on Justice Equality Defence and Women's Rights. Broadcasting Unit, Houses of the Oireachtas, Leinster House, Dublin 2., Jan 28, 2004; cuid33382 (Box 28A, Object 4)
    - Curious Journey: The Fight for Irish Freedom. International Digital Centre, Inc., New York, undated; cuid33383 (Box 27, Object 3)
    - Events in Short Strand houses being attacked; John Reid Visit Cruncher Singing, May 2002 - Aug 2002; cuid33384 (Box 27, Object 4)
    - "First Tuesday" A documentary on the Guildford Four; "Innocent or Guilty" A Documentary on the Birmingham Six; "Dear Sarah" A film. "Who Bombed Birmingham?" A film. "This tape has been digitally transferred and/or professionally dpulicated by Hennessy Headquarters D/B/A Irish Video, 5824 Broadway, NY 212-601-3833", undated; cuid33385 (Box 27, Object 5)
    - BBC Program (3 tapes) IDC, undated; cuid33386 (Box 28, Object 10-12)
    - Frontline: "Behind the Mask: The IRA and Sinn Fein" FROL603, 60 min. (3 copies), undated; cuid33387 (Box 27, Object 6-8)
    - Gerry Adams in South Florida Parts 1 and 2 (first copy), May 1996; cuid33388 (Box 27, Object 9-10)
    - Gerry Adams in South Florida Part 1 and 2 (second copy), May 1996; cuid33389 (Box 28, Object 1-2)
    - Interview with Caroline Moore of Derry City. Conducted by Mr. Kevin Harris, Attorney at Law. Merriam, Kansas. Includes note: Dear Frank: We are sending you this taped interview of Caroline Mooore who describes life in Northern Ireland Under the pressures of the security forces. We hope that it will be useful to you in your review of the police services. Your truly, Andy Somers" Irish American Unity Conference, National Office, DC, Feb 21, 1999; cuid33390 (Box 28, Object 3)
    - ITV's "Dispatches" Channel #4; Broadcast, approx 27 min, Feb 4, 1999; cuid33391 (Box 28, Object 4)
    - Panorama, Jun 21, 1999; cuid33392 (Box 28, Object 5)
    - Paul O'Dwyar [sic] R.I.P., undated; cuid33393 (Box 28, Object 6, Box Digitized Access Files, File aia008_cuid33393)
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
      Duration: 102 min.
    - Spanish Civil War Reunion in Barcelona. G.H. (George Harrison), undated; cuid33394 (Box 28, Object 7, Box Digitized Access Files, File aia008_cuid33394)
      Duration: 51 min.
    - Think About Tomorrow: Amnesty International's Student Action. Narrated by Corey Glover. AI Student Action Office, Washington DC, undated; cuid33395 (Box 28, Object 9)
    - Mayo 1951-1959: Mayo's Historic Return to an All-Ireland Final. An RTE Production., 1989; cuid33396 (Box 28A, Object 5)